- Do you know, that carrying
on the family tradition
Nancy Sinatra has unbelievably
because it happens just once
not very many times in a career
Nancy Sinatra's come up
with the number one record
in the country, and I'm
gonna ask her to sing it
not only for me, but
for her father and Jilly
who are down at
Miami Beach Night
And the number is "These
Boots are Made for Walking"
She has a golden
record because she sold
over a million copies of this
Let's have a wonderful welcome
for her, Nancy Sinatra
(audience applauding)
(upbeat music)
(boots stomping)
♪ You keep sayin' you
got somethin' for me ♪
♪ Somethin' you call
love, but confess ♪
♪ You've been a'messin' ♪
♪ Where you shouldn't've
been a'messin' ♪
♪ And now someone else is
gettin' all your best ♪
♪ These boots are
made for walkin' ♪
♪ And that's just
what they'll do ♪
♪ One of these
days these boots ♪
♪ Are gonna walk all over you ♪
(upbeat music)
- Yeah
(boots stomping)
♪ You keep lyin' when
you oughta be truthin' ♪
♪ And you keep losing
when you oughta not bet ♪
♪ You keep samin' when
you oughta be a'changin' ♪
♪ Now what's right is right ♪
♪ But you ain't been right yet ♪
♪ My boots are
made for walkin' ♪
♪ And that's just
what they'll do ♪
♪ One of these
days these boots ♪
♪ Are gonna walk all over you ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Now, you keep playin' where
you shouldn't be playin' ♪
♪ And you keep thinkin' that
you'll never get burnt, ha ♪
♪ I just found me a brand
new box of matches, yeah ♪
♪ And what he knows you
ain't had the time to learn ♪
♪ Now, my boots are
made for walkin' ♪
♪ And that's just what
they're gonna do ♪
♪ One of these
days these boots ♪
♪ Are gonna walk all over you ♪
♪ Now you put on your boots ♪
♪ And I'll put on mine ♪
♪ And we'll go walkin',
honey, any old time, now ♪
(upbeat music)
(audience applauding)
- Congratulations
Congratulations on your act
You know, when you
were singing there
I was thinking
years and years ago
when my daughter
was going to UCLA
I called up your father
Frank and asked him
if he'd go over to UCLA
and appear at an affair for her
and Frank has often told me
that she was standing
there reading, you know
doing her lessons
standing under a lamp
on the campus when he showed up
and I'm here tonight, I'm
introducing you, and...
- It's all in the family, right?
- It really is
all in the family
Let's have a wonderful hand
for a fine young woman
Thank you
(audience applauding)
Come here, Nancy Sinatra
They will never forgive me
Here (indistinct)
(audience applauding)
Thank you